Amanda Seales, please sit all the way
down because at this point you're a
troll and we really don't care what you
have to say. But please, we're going to
get into this today because come to the
front of the class because you're about
to get read. Yes, ma'am, you. So, at
this point like I said, Amanda Seales is
problematic. She's always on the wrong
side of right and she always has her
mouth talking about something and always
wants to have the unpopular opinion or
be the contrarian because at this point
like I said, she just wants to be anti
whatever else everyone else is. So,
basically, she got her happy behind on
this internet basically siding with
Cheyenne Bryant because of the fact
Cheyenne Bryant was so brilliant on her
podcast and she feels that, "Oh, why
it's a wag that she lied about her
credentials. She doesn't find it harmful
to anyone because she helped a lot of
people and you know, a lot of people
aren't real doctors like Maya Angelou
wasn't a real doctor."
First of all, sweetheart, Maya Angelou
never told anyone that she went to a
university and got a PhD and got a real
doctorate. Maya Angelou never tried to
lie and manipulate people. Okay, Maya
Angelou was straightforward and stood in
who she was and stood in her truth and
Dr. Cheyenne Bryant is not doing that.
So, what are you talking about? Then she
was claiming that, "Oh, because what
she's doing
what she's doing is not harmful." How is
it not harmful? How is that not harmful?
She is playing with mental health. She
is someone who is not qualified, someone
who does not have a true doctorate, who
is going around diagnosing people,
saying that she's a therapist, giving
all of this advice which is not
evidence-based practice information,
which is opinionated,
and she's trying to hide behind that by
saying she's a life coach. If you are a
true If you are a true therapist, if you
have a master's in all this counseling
and psychology and PhD and stuff like
that, then why can't you say that you
are a therapist? Oh, you're not working
under a license
because um you no longer because you're
making more money, but no license
exists. Like, how is that not harmful?
How is not playing with people's mental
health
not harmful? But then again,
I we have to pull this back a little bit
because Amanda uh Seales is the same one
who stated that she has autism, which
was self-diagnosed. So, she doesn't care
about credentials. She's someone who's
harmful as well. But let's also talk
about how much of a hypocrite she is
because when she was on the Shannon
Sharpe Show, she also said that because
she has degrees and has master's, she's
an expert in this inform
expert in those fields, and that she
knows what she's saying because she went
to school for that.
So, then on the other side of your neck,
you're saying that her credentials don't
matter because she's brilliant and she's
helping people. Girl, bye. Sit down.
And then for her to have a wild hair up
her ass about Kamala Harris because she
saying oh, because she don't understand
why black people are so upset at
Cheyenne Bryant, but they should be more
upset at Kamala Harris. Like, Kamala
Harris because she's for genocide and
whatever and is a Zionist. But at the
same time,
who's running the country?
Okay, that's what I thought. So, please
have several seats. Like, Amanda Seales,
you were a promising actress.
You had this little comedy career going.
You were probably like authorship, all
of this stuff. And then for whatever
reason you went straight left. You want
to argue with people, you always want to
have the unpopular opinion, you always
want to go go on the other side of
things so just so you can argue and go
back and forth with people because
you're bored, you have nothing else to
do, and then you get mad and come back
on the internet talking about what you
don't understand what people are talking
about. You're just going to go back to
what you were doing, and that's why you
don't like getting on social media. I
can't tell that you don't like getting
on social media cuz you get on social
media all the time you got something
stupid and ignorant to say. I don't care
how many degrees you have, I don't care
how much of knowledge, political, social
things that you think that you know,
honey, you really have a personality
issue and possibly a personality
disorder, but I'm not going to diagnose
you because we're not doing that here
today. But uh yeah, I'll let I'll leave
the diagnosing to you since you also
diagnose people as well.
Anyways,
that's all I got to say, ain't got
nothing else, and y'all have a good day.
Thanks.